{
    "id": "c690d843f5b14c92ba3775d22558be28",
    "title": "Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The winners …………………………. by all.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "have congratulated",
                "were congratulating",
                "were congratulated"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9ae41423c48f4dd9b57244d8d9348ac1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………………. after he complained of chest pain.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "has hospitalized",
                "was hospitalized",
                "had hospitalized"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b3a8717a85e74bd8ad0e1848163fd10c"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ……………………… that the prices of oil will increase after the election.",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, the passive form is made with is/am/are + past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "is speculated",
                "is speculating",
                "has speculated"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "92290089362645a5abddeb6f0c49d536"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………… for possessing firearms.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "arrested",
                "has arrested",
                "was arrested"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8ad976a8c1ad41e692bd6ab8d6e91def"
        },
        {
            "question": "My questions ……………………….",
            "description": "The active form is 'They have answered my questions'. In the present perfect, the passive form is made with has/have + past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "have answered",
                "has been answered",
                "have been answered"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eed256f609944bbf969b2e96d0e20595"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… to their party.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't invite",
                "was not invited",
                "have not invited"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c4cd1f83ac3a489fa4dbe9eeaf36e452"
        },
        {
            "question": "The parcel ……………………… in the morning.",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, the passive form is made with was/were + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "sent",
                "has sent",
                "was sent"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3317f99b9c044bc9b8656ceff42f4c6d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The results ……………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have announced",
                "have been announced",
                "had announced"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2390ee5d599949d5adeff3c88346aba9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Football ………………………… all over the world.",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, the passive form is made with is/am/are + past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "played",
                "is played",
                "have played"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e591813b24974789a8d7cfb0989d4377"
        },
        {
            "question": "The label …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should not remove",
                "should not removed",
                "should not be removed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "730f8d4641e944b5b96b4fd045b44935"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do not accept this product if the seal …………………….",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, the passive form is made with is/am/are + past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "breaks",
                "has broken",
                "is broken"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "40d707562cf44f69b82aeb4fc3dca38f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………… by millions of people all over the world.",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, the passive form is made with is/am/are + past participle form of the verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "admired",
                "has admired",
                "is admired"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d907704902c24274b8b3641e511d35d6"
        }
    ]
}